CONTACT - Based in Bristol



will_kewell@btinternet.com



07816 280436/+44 7816 280436

SKILLS

- People orientated, calm and confident disposition.
- Communication skills, both written and verbal.
- Team working developed through participation in team sport and future problem solving at school.
- Confident working in a team in high pressure situations.
- Strong attention to detail.
- Adaptable and flexible.
- Proficient Java and Python programmer, with experience in other programming languages.
- Object Oriented Programming Skills.
- Experience with design & development cycle and full stack software development.
- Experience with Git.
- SQL & relational database skills and full stack web application development experience, use of technologies including Spring Boot and React.
- Good understanding of Cyber Security concepts.
- Good understanding of IP Networking concepts.
- Experience with Linux operating systems.
- Problem solving and strong mathematical background.
- Spanish language skills.
- Proficient in Microsoft Office, including Access, Excel, Word and PowerPoint which I have used for my academic assignments.

William Kewell

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am an able and hardworking individual and have recently graduated from Southampton University achieving a BSc in Computer Science. My goal is to kickstart my career with a role in technology, working in a fast moving and energetic environment. Proficient programmer, eager to learn and develop my existing skills.

Qualified NPLQ Pool Lifeguard, having worked as a Lifeguard during the past 6 years, currently working part time at David Lloyd Bristol Westbury.

EDUCATION

Southampton University BSc Computer Science

Achievement: Second Class Honours (Upper Division) (2.1)

Queen Elizabeth's Hospital Bristol

A level subjects & achievements: Mathematics (A*); Further Mathematics (A); Physics (A)

AS subjects & achievements: Mathematics (A); Further Mathematics (A); Spanish (B); Physics (B); ICT (A)

GCSE subjects & achievements: Mathematics (A*); Physics (A*); Chemistry (A*); Biology (A*); Spanish (A*); First Language English (A*); Literature (English) (A); History (A); Geography (A)

WORK HISTORY

Lifeguard David Lloyd Bristol Westbury, Bristol

- Supervised a busy members pool, ensuring the safety of adults & children alike.
- Effectively handling members' queries and complaints in order to ensure a good customer experience.
- Collaborated efficiently in a team of experienced lifeguards to ensure the smooth operation of the pool and proactive prevention of accidents.

2017-2021

2008-2017

January 2022 – Present

William Kewell

 Lifeguard Clifton College, Bristol Supervised a school/leisure centre pool. Ensured the safety of children from a holiday kid's club and language school. 	May 2017 – March 2020
Orange (Telecommunications), Bristol Work experience • Shadowed telecommunications professionals in their daily work activities. • Developed an interest and understanding in the technology/telecommunications industry.	Summer 2015
CERTIFICATIONS	
CERTIFICATIONS	
National Pool Lifeguard Qualification (NPLQ) Bristol University, Clifton, Bristol	Oct 2021
National Pool Lifeguard Qualification (NPLQ)	Oct 2021 Oct 2015 & Sept 2017
National Pool Lifeguard Qualification (NPLQ) Bristol University, Clifton, Bristol STA Level 2 Award for Pool Lifeguard (QCF) STA Level 2 Award in Emergency First Aid at Work	Oct 2015 &
National Pool Lifeguard Qualification (NPLQ) Bristol University, Clifton, Bristol STA Level 2 Award for Pool Lifeguard (QCF) STA Level 2 Award in Emergency First Aid at Work (QCF)	Oct 2015 &
National Pool Lifeguard Qualification (NPLQ) Bristol University, Clifton, Bristol STA Level 2 Award for Pool Lifeguard (QCF) STA Level 2 Award in Emergency First Aid at Work (QCF) ADDITIONAL ACHIEVEMENTS Represented the UK at the International Future	Oct 2015 & Sept 2017